康卡斯特旗下公司
環球影片公司
遠鑒字幕組
遠鑒字幕組 榮譽製作
[Visionary] 0day-sub
更多更新電影字幕 敬請
關注微博 遠鑒字幕組v
或加入QQ群 391250217
翻譯
william2568 我問這瓜保熟麼 Sue牧師
校對
特效
雲中漫步wfaith
一年2400次
一周44次
一天9次
每48分鐘
就有一宗銀行搶劫
這是全球銀行搶劫之都
洛杉磯
花旗銀行
保持
距離
15米
賊 巢
加迪納        南洛杉磯
早上 5:14
No, no, no, bro! We're not here for you! Don't even think about it!
別 別 別 兄弟！我們不是衝著你們來的！想都別想！
Don't you move, motherfucker!
別動 他媽的！
Hands away from the weapon, bro! Fucking relax!
手離武器遠點兒 兄弟！你他媽的給我放鬆！
3170. We're being held up.
我是3170 我們被圍住了
Armor piercing rounds are chambered in this firearm!
穿甲子彈已經上膛了！
Please don't be the asshole who forces me to use them.
別逼我開火
Take your foot off the gas,
腳從腳踏板上拿開
press the unlock button, and step out of the vehicle,
按下開門鍵 然後從車裡出來
or we will forcibly remove you!
否則我會強行把你拖出來！
Fucking do it! Now!
快點 給我滾出來
Your choice! Go!
這是你逼我的 動手
What the fuck!
他媽的
He fucking went for his gun.
他媽的他是去摸他的槍了！
He spilled his fucking coffee.
他媽的他是把咖啡給灑了！
霍 桑
Shit.
見鬼！
Gardena, 30 seconds out.
加迪納 30秒
Copy.
收到
Thirty out. Hustle!
剩下30秒了 快點！
- Pop it. - Ready.
- 炸開它 - 準備好了
Man on!
上！
Out of fucking time.
都他媽沒時間了！
Prepare to engage.
準備好交火
Contact right!
右邊有敵人
Range 100. Suppressive fire.
100米 火力壓製
Contact left!
左邊有敵人！
Dispatch, 10-97. LAPD is on scene.
1097出動 洛杉磯警察已到現場
We are under heavy fire!
我們遭到了火力壓製！
Fuck!
操你媽的！
Motherfucker!
他媽的
Whoa, whoa. I got you. I got you.
我來掩護你
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
快走 快走
What the fuck was that?
他媽的剛剛是怎麼回事？
Did you see him go for his gun?
你看見他去碰槍了?
I don't know. I just saw Bosco lit him up.
我不知道 我只看到博斯科把他崩了
Take the second left into the tunnel.
第二個路口左轉進入隧道
Hug the airport. Take the tunnel.
順著機場 進入隧道
Go right on Doty.
在多提右轉
Right on Doty.
多提右轉
威明頓
Make sure you take care of those weapons.
確保你們管好你們的槍
I don't want any accidental discharges.
不希望有槍走火
- What are you looking at him for? - Ray.
- 你看著他說這話幹嘛？- 雷
I'm not talking to him. I'm talking to you.
我不是在跟他說 我是跟你說
What the fuck was that?
剛剛他媽的到底怎麼回事？
What else did you fuck up, huh?
你他媽還搞砸什麼了？
You sure you were clean all the way home?
你確定回來的時候沒被跟蹤嗎？
Catch any tails?
有尾巴嗎？
Where did Marcus take those rounds?
馬庫斯哪裡中槍了？
Femoral artery. He's done.
股動脈 他死定了
Well, we knew the risks.
我們知道這行有風險的
Shit popped off. We handled it. That's it.
突發狀況 我們處理好了 沒事兒了
Hey, B.
嘿 B
Get back over there.
回去那裡
See who responded. It was probably LASD.
看看是誰接手了 可能是洛杉磯治安局
They'll supersede Gardena,
他們比加迪納警察職權大
but if it's Major Crimes, we've got a problem.
但如果這次行動被立為重案 我們就有麻煩了
All clear? No GPS?
都沒問題了吧？沒發現有GPS追蹤器吧？
It's one of the old models, man. We good.
有一個老款的 已經處理掉了
We've got to get this patched up.
我們需要把禍給補上！
We need this clean.
需要乾淨利落！
You good?
你還好嗎？
We're cop killers now.
我們現在成了警察殺手了
梅利曼
聖佩德羅
Jesus Christ!
天！
You scared the shit out of me, babe. Can't do that.
你嚇我一跳 寶貝 你不能那樣做
What are you doing right now?
你現在在幹嘛？
You erasing your recent calls?
刪除最近的通話記錄？
My phone? What do you mean?
我的電話裡的？你什麼意思？
I don't know how to work this fucking thing. You know that.
我根本不會使用這個鬼東西 你知道的
"I don't know how to work this fucking thing. You know that."
“我根本不會使用這個鬼東西 你知道的”
Come on.
別裝了
Babe, we really have to go through this right now?
寶貝 我們現在真的要為這個吵架嗎？
Where you been?
你去哪了？
It's 6:00 a.m. Where have you been?
早上6點了 你去哪了？
Been at work?
在工作？
Surveillance? Robbing drug dealers? Because you smell like a stripper.
監視？搶劫毒販？因為你全身都是脫衣舞娘味兒
Of course, I was at work.
我當然是在工作
It's funny 'cause I got this text.
那很奇怪 我收到了這條短信
What was so hot, then?
什麼那麼性感啊？
Is that a work text?
是工作短信嗎？
You fucked up. You text me instead.
你自己腦子進水了 發錯給我了
Who does that?
什麼人啊？
It's street theater, babe. It's not what it looks like. I'm sorry.
只是和朋友吹吹牛的 不是你想的那樣 我很抱歉
me too
我也是
We're going to go to Auntie's house
我們要去小姨家
because Daddy's got to do a little work on the house.
因為爸爸要把房子維修下
And we have something else to do.
我們還有別的事要做
- Come on. - What the fuck?
- 快點 - 搞他媽什麼啊
Hey, yo.
嘿 你
It's gonna be too loud for you guys, okay?
這裡對你們來說太吵了
- Deb? Deb? - Will you put this on?
- 黛比 黛比 - 把這個穿上
- Is Daddy coming with us? - What are you doing, Deb?
- 爸爸一起來嗎？- 黛比 你要幹嘛？
What the fuck are you doing?
你他媽的要幹嘛？
- It will be too loud for you guys. - Wifey, wifey.
- 對你們來說會很吵的 - 老婆 老婆
Seriously, what are you doing?
你認真的嗎？你在幹嘛？
Is Daddy coming with us?
爸爸和我們一起來嗎？
No, Daddy does not have enough time for us right now.
不會 爸爸現在沒有時間給我們
- Seriously... That's nice. That's nice. - Can you put this on here?
- 你認真的嗎？真是太棒了 太棒了  - 你能把這個放下嗎
Hey, honey. Mommy didn't mean that, okay?
嘿 甜心 媽媽其實不是那個意思 知道了嗎？
Hey, sweetie, come here. Mommy didn't mean that, okay?
小甜心 過來 媽媽不是那個意思 知道嗎？
She didn't mean that, okay? Sweetie, you okay?
她不是那個意思 好嗎？你還好嗎 寶貝
Yeah, great. Great.
好 好極了
Hey. Come here, honey.
過來寶貝
I'm not going to be able to make it right now,
我現在暫時可能做不到
but I'm gonna come a little later, okay?
但是晚一點兒... 好嗎
All right. Come here. Give me a hug.
過來抱抱我
- Time to go right now. - Christ sake.
- 到時間要走了 - 我靠
Will you slow it down a second?
你慢點兒好不好
Give Daddy some rest. He's real tired.
讓爸爸休息會兒 他累了
- Right, hon? - What...
對吧甜心
Deb. Deb. Deb, will you slow it down a second?
黛比 黛比 你能緩一緩嗎？
- We're going to walk this way... - Deb.
- 我們走這邊  - 黛比
Okay, watch your step. Here we go.
注意台階   慢著
Deb, can you slow it...
黛比 慢著
Okay. Come on.
快點
Let's go. We're going to put your sister in first.
我們走嘍 先把你妹妹放進車裡
Here we go. Okay, baby, ready?
好了寶貝準備好了嗎？
Sweetie, it's going to be okay, sweetie. Okay?
甜心 會沒事的 甜心 知道了嗎？
Let's go.
我們走
Okay, put your bags in there. You wanna put your sister in the seat?
把你的包放這兒 你需要讓你妹妹坐這兒
Where's the pink bag?
粉色的包去哪了？
Have you lost your fucking mind?
操他媽的瘋了嗎？
Oh, great language right in front of my daughter.
哦 在我女兒面前說這麼粗俗的話
Great fathering!
爸爸典範！
Nice. Nice. Dropping F-bombs in front of my daughters.
很好 很好 在我女兒面前說“操”
- "My kids," huh? "My kids?" - Great fathering!
- 說什麼“我的孩子”“我的孩子”的  - 你這爸爸當的真行
Gonna find a guy whose cock actually gets hard for me.
我會找一個在我面前會硬的男人
Deb, Deb, Deb. Stop!
黛比 黛比 停下來！
Please don't do this.
請別這樣
Please.
求你了
This is a little hard. You're just scared right now, okay? You're confused.
這有點兒難 你只是現在有點兒害怕 你不知道是怎麼回事
Out of the way, Nick. Get out of the way, Nick.
尼克 讓開 讓開 尼克！
Get the fuck out of here, you fucker!
你他媽的給我滾開
You motherfucker!
你這個混蛋！
You get back! You understand me, you motherfucker?
混蛋 你聽見了嗎？你這個混蛋！
- Stay away from us! - Nice. Nice.
離我們遠點兒
Good. Good.
很好 很好
Okay. Mommy's okay.
沒事 我沒事
See you later.
晚些見
Morning
早上好
Yup.
說吧
Yeah
好的
老大尼克
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
你一定是在和我開玩笑吧
Well, that looks like it hurt.
看起來很疼啊
No?
不是嗎？
Good morning, fellow officers.
早上好 各位同事
I take it he's a bad guy.
嗯 我猜他應該是壞人
You mean the guy with the black body armor,
你是指這個穿著黑色護甲
shotgun, and gas mask?
配有散彈槍和防毒面具的人嗎？
That's very funny. We know who he is yet?
你挺風趣啊 弄清楚他是誰了嗎？
Rough night?
昨晚很不順？
Yes. Next subject?
是的 換個話題
You're not looking so hot there, bubba.
你今天看著不那麼性感啊
I think he looks amazing.
我覺得他看著很棒啊
I've got enough toxins in me to turn the Gaza Strip into a Gay Pride parade.
我體內的毒素足以把加沙地帶變成同性戀大遊行
You better start downing the POM juice, big man. We've got a piss test Friday.
你還是少喝點兒“石榴汁”吧 周五尿檢
Thursday.
是周四
What, like you Mormons have been drinking wheatgrass all fucking month?
你們他媽的摩門教的人是不是這個月都在喝青草汁兒？
Please.
別這樣
You got another one of those? I'm fucking starving.
這個你還有嗎？我快餓死了
Yeah, there's a couple that don't have blood.
還有倆個沒沾上血的
I think it's one of the pinkies with the sprinkles.
好像就是那個粉色的 有巧克力粒兒的
That's some real donut.
這甜甜圈真是不錯啊
Those are horrendous, dude.
老兄這些太可怕了
Hey. You guys push back the perimeter.
嘿 夥計們 把警戒線往後拉點
Need to extend the crime scene, okay? Too goddamn small.
犯罪現場需要擴大保護範圍 明白？範圍太他媽的小了
- You got it. - What's the tally?
- 明白 - 現在有什麼數據？
We've got four dead, six on the way to the hospital.
四個當場死了 六個送醫院了
- But they'll be all right. - Fuck.
- 應該沒有生命危險  - 操
Ambushed them as they were coming to get breakfast.
來買早餐的時候被埋伏了
Surrounded the truck.
他們的車被包圍了
This poor fool right here was trying to do what he gets paid to do.
這個可憐鬼 只是想做好自己的工作
AP rounds blasted through the windshield took him out.
穿甲彈打穿了前玻璃 把他給崩出來了
They took the truck, Gardena police lost them under Hawthorne Municipal.
他們搶走了卡車 加迪納警察在霍索恩跟丟了
They knew the route.
他們對路線很熟
Picked it because it was next to Municipal Airport,
選擇加迪納是因為它就在市機場旁邊
knew the restricted air space meant no ghetto bird air support.
因為飛行限制 所以他們知道不會有直升機追蹤
We're dealing with a different animal here, boys.
我們面對的劫匪不一般啊 夥計們
Talk to the armored car company? What was the haul?
跟裝甲卡車公司談過了嗎？丟了多少？
They were en route to a bank pickup for a Fed drop.
他們是在去銀行的路上 幫聯邦銀行取東西
But there was nothing in the truck.
但是車上是空的
Nothing in the truck?
空的？
They stole a fucking empty armored truck?
他們他媽的偷了倆空的裝甲卡車？
Yup.
是的
Why the fireworks?
為什麼開槍？
One of the vics said the messenger went for his gun. That's when it popped off.
有個受害人說車警去摸槍了 那就是開打的原因
Genius.
真是個天才！
Okay, the SUV, what have we got?
好吧 那輛城市四驅 有什麼線索？
That's a cold car.
沒什麼有用的線索
VIN's been pried off. Plates are stolen. No prints on it.
引擎號撕掉了 車牌是偷的 沒有指紋
They bleach-bombed it.
他們還用漂白水給它炸了
Right. Take it to SID. Tent that fucker. Swab it. Detail it.
好吧 把它送到科學偵察科 罩起來 棉簽全抹一遍 不放過任何細節
Ah, fuck. I can't deal with this retard factory this early.
操 這麼早就讓我和這個低能兒周旋
One of you guys handle it?
你們誰來吧
It's all you, bro.
兄弟 只有你了
Thank you.
謝了
All right, witnesses, donut shop guy?
好吧 有目擊者嗎？甜甜圈店員？
He saw them, and they looked right at him,
他看見他們了 他們直勾勾的對視了
but, for some reason, they left him alone.
但是不知道為什麼沒動他
Okay, pull all video surveillance and plate readers. Do a Palantir run.
好 收集所有的監控錄像 車牌讀取器 做個大數據篩查
Talk to DOT, okay?
跟交通部門聯絡
Pull it all together, and meet me at the office.
都收集好之後 我們在辦公室碰頭
And find me that fucking truck.
把那該死的裝甲車給我找回來
Big Nick, original gangsta cop in the flesh.
老大尼克 警察血液中的原始黑幫份子
Lobbin' Bob. Huh?
羅賓 '鮑勃'對吧？
How's that mean tennis game?
你這個網球高手還有繼續打網球嗎？
Look at you, man.
看看你 夥計！
Where'd you pick that up? Nice suit.
你在哪買的？很不錯的西服
Well, not where you're shopping. I can't afford it.
肯定不是在你消費的地方買的 那地方的東西我可買不起
I mean, how does a county sheriff
我說 一個小小的鎮警
pay for such a beautiful piece of men's fashion?
哪來的錢買這麼漂亮的夾克？
You kidding me? This piece of shit? Nah, this is garbage.
這坨狗屎？這是垃圾
Look at you.
看看你
This thing's tits!
這東西太贊了
You must pull all kinds of ass sporting that, no?
你得什麼屎勾當都幹才能買得起它吧 是吧？
Nick, you know what? I can't. I can't.
好吧 我不能 我不想說了..
It's too early in the morning for your fucking circus.
大清早的我可沒閒心看你在這耍猴
You just threw a donut in the hot zone.
你剛剛把一個甜甜圈扔進案發現場裡了
- No. I did not. - Yeah, you did.
- 我沒有吧！ - 你有！
I did? That was fucking wrong.
我扔了？那樣做太他媽錯了
It was. I don't like you, Nick, or how you handle police business...
是的 我不喜歡你 尼克 不喜歡你處理警察事務的方法...
Hey, hey, hey. What's up with that?
嘿 你什麼意思？
I like you.
我可喜歡你
Aside from the fact that you're a vegetarian.
儘管你是個素食主義者
Vegan! I'm a vegan.
是嚴格素食者！我是嚴格素食者
- Vegetarians, they eat milk... - Yeah, sorry to hear that.
- 素食者是喝牛奶的  - 哦 我為你感到遺憾
What are you doing here anyway, huh?
你到底來幹嘛的？
No legal tender was stolen. It isn't Federal.
這案子沒涉及法幣丟失 就不屬於聯邦案件
Yet.
暫時不是
You're pausing for dramatic effect?
你定格是為了營造戲劇效果？
You're such a big, bad lieutenant.
你簡直就是個大壞警官！
- I know. I know. - Yeah.
- 我知道 我知道  - 是啊
Can I go now, Dad? I'm kind of hungry.
我能走了嗎 老爸？我有點兒餓了
So Gardena showed up, and they secured the scene,
加迪納警察來了 控制了現場
and then these clowns took over.
然後這些小丑給接手了
Who are they, LASD?
他們是誰？洛杉磯治安局的？
Yeah, Sheriff's. They must be. Look at this clown right here.
是的 他們肯定是治安局的 看看這個小丑
He seemed to be in charge.
他好像是頭兒
You recognize him?
你對他有印象嗎？
He played football at South.
他在南邊玩過足球
Remember Endo? Filipino dude the cops killed?
記得安德歐嗎？警察幹掉的菲律賓人
Yeah.
嗯
罪與罰 洛杉磯縣風格
That's the cop who blasted him.
就是他幹掉的安德歐
Runs Major Crimes.
他主管大案的
Get to know your enemy, boys.
要知己知彼 兄弟們
洛杉磯縣警察局
Who's running this crew?
誰是這團夥的主使？
Probably two, three guys that can pull this off, max.
可能有2-3人有能力做到
Why steal an armored truck with nothing in it?
為什麼要偷一輛空的裝甲卡車？
Bad tip, they probably botched it.
可能消息有誤 白乾了
Why didn't they dump it, then?
那為什麼沒有把車扔掉？
- I'll check the salvage yards. - All of them.
- 我查查廢車場 - 所有的都查
And how'd they know about a transfer from the casino to the Fed,
他們怎麼知道聯邦機構要從賭場運東西？
especially one that wasn't scheduled through the regular carrier? How?
尤其是這次行程都不在常規計劃裡 他們是怎麼知道的？
It was an inside job, bro. It had to be.
肯定是有內奸 錯不了
Oh, fuck. Give me the Pepto.
操 把止瀉藥給我
Okay, inside job, but where?
好吧 有內奸 那是哪個環節出錯了
Right? Was it the casino, the bank, the Fed, the fucking donut shop? Where?
賭場？銀行？還是他媽的甜甜圈店？哪個？
What about Merrimen?
有沒有可能是梅利曼乾的呢？
When did he parole again?
他是什麼時候假釋的？
- Eight months ago. - Eight months ago?
- 8個月前 - 8個月前？
We need to find that fucking truck.
我們需要找到那輛該死的裝甲車
Have we still got a tail on that Wilson kid?
威爾森那孩子你還跟著呢麼？
Yeah.
嗯
The one who was hanging out with Merrimen?
就是老和梅利曼一起的那個
What bar did he work in?
在哪個酒吧工作來著？
- Hofbrau. - Ziggy's Hofbrau.
- 哈夫布勞 - 基奇的哈夫布勞
Let's pay him a visit.
我們去會會他
...some Wi-Fi? No? We better check his videos.
有Wi-Fi嗎？沒有？我們最好看看他的視頻
- Thanks. - All right.
- 謝謝 - 沒事
Wolfgang, talk to me.
沃夫岡 要點什麼？
- Donnie, I'm tapped out. - No problem.
- 唐尼 我沒錢了 - 沒事
Put it on my tab, all right?
幫我記賬上吧 好嗎？
- Of course, man, I got you. - Thank you.
- 當然 兄弟 我幫你搞定 - 謝謝
Have a good night.
晚安
Are we doing this?
我們做這票嗎？
Yeah, man. All right, man.
是的 兄弟 好的兄弟
To money and women.
為我們的錢和女人乾杯
That we don't have.
還沒到手的
How do you remember everybody's order like that?
你是怎麼記住那麼多人點的酒的？
I can't remember the last four of my social.
我連我社保卡的最後4位都記不住
Lots of reps man.
不停的重複 兄弟
I'm in complete control of my environment. People don't even know.
我周邊的環境是被我完全掌控的 他們根本不知道
- Hey, man, time to go. - Okay.
- 嘿 兄弟 該走了 - 好的
Wrap it up.
收拾收拾
- Just a little bit. - Yeah, yeah.
- 就一點點了  - 好 好
- Ziggy's going to kill me. - Shit, not going to finish.
- 嗯 基奇會殺了我 - 操 喝不完了
A gift.
給你的禮物
How about a tip?
小費呢？
We got you last time.
上次給了
Oh, yeah, you got me last...
給了？
That's not how it works.
規矩不是這樣的
Okay, really? Zoo animals.
就給這點兒？這幫畜生
Need change?
需要找零？
That's for you, Fräulein.
是給你的 小妞
Thanks.
謝了
Are there always so many cops in here?
總有這麼多警察來這嗎？
Last place I'd think they'd be.
我覺得他們不會選擇來這兒
Yeah, this their spot. You know, cheap liquor.
嗯 這是他們的地盤 這的酒很便宜
Right.
嗯
Yeah, there also is a lot of shady cats in here, huh?
這裡什麼樣的壞人都有 是吧？
Yeah, it's kind of neutral grounds, you know?
嗯 是的 這裡算是個中立地段吧 懂嗎？
Rick's in Casablanca type shit.
就像 瑞克在卡薩布蘭卡那樣 那種
You must've heard some stories in this place.
你在這肯定聽到了不少故事
You know, give him a couple of drinks, steak on his plate,
嗯 給他們兩杯酒 來一碟牛排
some nice women around him,
美麗的女人纏繞
he'll tell you his darkest secrets.
他就會告訴你他最陰暗的秘密
Loose lips sink ships.
言多必失 禍從口出
Ain't that the truth.
說的不假啊
Mmm, what about you?
你呢？
Pull a lot of pussy in here? Yeah?
在這可以釣到好多女人 對吧？
Come on.
說說吧
- I do well for myself. - Yeah.
- 我自己一個人挺好的  - 是啊
I'd fuck you.
我都願意操你的
Kidding.
開玩笑的
All right.
好吧
I'm out.
我要走了
See you later, man.
再見兄弟
Yeah.
是啊
Look forward to it.
很期待再見
- Fräulein. - Dude, what the fuck are you...
- 小妞！ - 操 你他媽的在幹嘛...
唐 尼
Fraulein, you're up. Yeah.
小妞 你醒了
What the fuck?
搞什麼
What's up, gangster?
還好嗎 混混？
Oh, Peaches.
哦 桃子
Oh, Fräulein, you're up.
哦 小妞 你起來了
Sit down. You sit right there.
坐下 你就坐這裡
What you walking so slow for, nigga?
兄弟你走那麼慢幹嘛？
I want you to sit right there. That's you right there.
坐那 你就坐那
- Look here. There's cigarettes. - Yeah.
- 看這兒 那是煙  - 嗯
Borracho!
布若丘！
I think y'all got me confused with somebody.
你們把我認錯成別人了
Hey, Sporto.
嘿
You want a blow job?
想讓小妞幫你口一下嗎？
Why my pants wet?
為什麼我的褲子是濕的？
Come on, man, if you and your Uncle Tom over here
兄弟們 如果你們和這位湯姆大叔在這
are into some homo shit, I'm good.
玩同性戀那一套 別打我的主意
Y'all just kill me now.
要不 你們現在就殺了我
You pissed yourself, bubba.
你自己給尿了 傻孩兒
It happens.
有時候會的
I had one of the girls here clean you up, so you're good.
這裡的女孩兒幫你洗了 你沒事的
But y'all got the wrong dude.
你抓錯人了
You got me confused with someone.
你把我認成別人了
But I'm going to let you know now, I ain't the one.
我現在就告訴你  我不是你要找的人
What'd you say?
你怎麼解釋？
Dude something?
說啥？
No, we're not mistaking you for anybody. Don't be a fucking smartass.
我們沒認錯你 別他媽的自作聰明
Arrested at 17 for GTA.
因為盜車17歲被捕
Tried and convicted as an adult.
作為成人案件被審判入罪
We know exactly who you are.
我們清楚的知道你是誰
Did a stint at county for attempted manslaughter.
殺人未遂在郡監獄服刑
Fastest speeding ticket in California history.
加利福尼亞歷史上速度最快的超速罰單就是開給你的
That's nice.
很牛啊
Fucking genius, man. How fast were you going?
真他媽有才 你當時開的多快？
178.
每小時178公里
Speed demon!
超速狂魔啊!
What did you say to the cop who pulled you over?
你和抓到你的警察是怎麼說的？
What reason did you give him?
用的什麼理由？
Told him they'd just paved the road.
我說他們剛把新路面鋪好
- I like him. - Ballsy.
- 我欣賞這小子！- 有種
Me gusta.
我喜歡
You may have a little pecker for a black dude.
也許作為黑人你的丁丁有些小
You may be a bed-wetter, but you've got some fucking style, buddy.
雖然你尿褲子 但是你他媽的還挺有個性的 兄弟
All right, girls, time to go.
就這樣吧 女士們 該走了
Grab your shoes. Grab your shit. Let's go.
拿好你們的鞋啊什麼的 都走吧
Time to go home to your babies.
回去喂你們的寶寶們
- All right, thanks for stopping by. - Excuse me.
- 謝謝過來  - 不好意思
You check this out, hot rod. You're a two-striker.
聽好 飛車手 你已經進去兩次了
You need to fucking look at me when I'm talking to you.
看著我 我他媽跟你說話呢
You're one mistake away from getting sex in the ass every time you shower.
再犯一次錯 你就得去監獄撿肥皂了
Some of them niggas got gas pumps.
有的那些黑人和輪胎蹦一樣粗
Now, personally, that shit don't sound like a lot of fun to me.
在我來看 這事聽起來挺沒趣的
What you think? How you feel about that?
你怎麼想的?感想如何？
Look, the dude in that picture is not even a regular at my bar.
照片裡那個男人都不是我酒吧的常客
Like, I've seen him a few times, but, you know, I don't associate myself...
我看見過他幾次 但我絕不會跟這種人...
Do you know what this means?
知道這個什麼意思嗎？
It means I am a member of a clique.
我是一個小集團的成員
It's kind of like being in a gang.
就像是個幫會
Sort of like a gang, only we have badges,
就像是一個幫會 但是我們都有警徽
which means you are done.
意思是你玩兒完了
He ain't lying.
他沒說謊
Let me ask you this.
這麼跟你說吧
Okay, do we look like the types who will arrest you?
你看我們跟之前抓你的那些警察一樣嗎？
Put you in handcuffs, drag you down to the station?
給你戴上手銬 把你拉到警察局那些？
I'm asking you a fucking question.
我他媽在問你話呢！
No. Not at all.
一點兒不像
Right, exactly.
對 說得對
We just shoot you. It's less paperwork.
我們可以直接就把你斃了 這樣還能少寫點兒報告
So tell me,
所以 說吧
what the fuck are you doing hanging out in that crew?
你他媽的跟那幫人一起在幹嘛呢？
You're a pussy.
你就是個膽小鬼
Those dudes are bad dudes.
他們都是大壞蛋
Great thieves but straight convicts.
大盜 有罪之人
What's Merrimen doing drinking beers with the likes of you for?
梅利曼和你這種人和啤酒在幹嘛？
Talk shop?
談工作?
You gonna hit the fucking Hofbrau?
你們要搶酒吧？
Take the place down, score, like, what, two grand in ones and fives?
把地方都拆了搶那5塊10塊的2000塊錢？
Is that what's afoot? I'll answer that for you.
你們準備這麼幹嘛？我都能替你回答
No, it fucking isn't.
肯定他媽不是啊
I don't know what crew you're speaking about, man.
我不知道你說的這幫人是誰
This dude just comes to my bar where I work...
那傢伙就是到我工作的酒吧喝酒
Stop. Shut up.
停 閉嘴
Come on, man. This is some weird shit. Just...
夠了吧 你們 我都被你們搞蒙了 就讓我...
You listen to me, fuckface.
聽著 操蛋臉
We don't give a shit about you.
我們才不在乎你
You in Merrimen's crew?
你是梅利曼團夥的成員嗎？
Huh? You hit the stadium?
體育場那票有你一份嗎？
You talky-talky now?
你現在想說話了嗎？
Yes, please.
是的 求你了
Fuck!
操!
I'm just the driver!
我只是司機！
They don't give me no gun. I don't do no gangster shit.
他們不給我槍 我沒參與幫會活動
They asked me to drive, so that's what I do.
他們讓我開車!所以我開車！
That's it. Fuck!
就那樣！操！
Why did Merrimen hijack an empty armored car?
為什麼梅利曼要搶一輛空的裝甲卡車？
I don't know, all right?
我不知道
They keep me in the dark for shit like this.
他們就怕我被抓了會亂講 所以都瞞著我
If the cops come down on me,
警察抓到我
I can't tell them shit if I don't know shit.
我什麼都不知道就不會亂說
Now y'all can hook me up to a lie detector,
你可以給我連上
a fucking polygraph, whatever y'all got.
他媽的測謊儀 你用什麼都可以
I'm telling you what I know, and that's all you'll get.
我知道的都告訴你們了 只有這些
Please, just let me the fuck go.
求你了 放了我吧
Fuck y'all, man. Let me go.
操 放了我吧
Well, I thought that was relatively convincing, hmm?
哇 我覺得你說的還挺能唬人的
Good stuff.
好演技
All right, when did you meet him?
好吧 你什麼時候見他的？
What do I get out of this?
我能得到什麼？
What do you get out of this? Well, your freedom for one.
你能得到什麼？嗯 一個是自由
Two,
二
you're not the bad guys.
你並不是壞人
We are.
而我們是
Couple months ago, they came through the bar,
幾個月前他們來到酒吧
and I served them a few drinks.
我給他們倒了幾杯酒
We started talking.
然後我們開始商議
Hey, Donnie, come here, man.
嘿 唐尼 過來 夥計
This is my boy, Bosco.
這是我的哥們博斯克
My brother for life. We deployed together.
我同生共死的兄弟 我們一起服役的
Hey, the kid can drive.
這孩子能開車
Okay.
好
Donnie, tell him about the Trans Am Series.
唐尼 跟他講講Am系列的運輸車
Drove Trans Am Series, like he said, for about a season.
我開過Am系列的運輸車 就像他說的 開過4個月
What were their names?
他們叫什麼？
Hawaiian dude,
夏威夷人
he had a homie, Bosco, white boy.
他的死黨博斯克是個白人
He was in the military, and he worked for DWP.
他之前服役過 之前在水利部工作
I told him I needed some extra money,
我跟他說我需要掙些外快
so he gave me a job.
所以他給了我一個工作
Who's that? Merrimen?
誰？梅利曼？
Merrimen.
梅利曼
Ray Merrimen.
雷 梅利曼
So what's up with this dude?
這人的底細搞清楚了嗎？
It's Marcus' boy.
馬庫斯的人
Worked with him over at the Hofbrau.
之前在哈夫布勞一起上班
Say he did some time with him at Wayside.
在維塞德監獄一起服過刑
He was a Marine for a minute.
他之前不是軍人麼？
Say the nigga can drive. He be cool.
他說能開車 就沒問題吧
All right, let's check him out.
好吧 我們去試探下他
Real smart dude.
他很聰明
He had just got out of prison from what I could tell.
我能看出他剛出獄
聯邦監獄
特米諾島
長灘島 加利福尼亞
You ready to roll, Ray?
準備好了嗎 雷？
514!
514號
Come on, let's cuff them up.
來 給他戴上手銬
You want any of your shit?
你的這些破爛還要嗎？
No.
不
Let's go.
走吧
See you soon, Ray.
很快再見 雷
No, you won't.
你見不著了
You look great, baby.
你氣色很好 寶貝
All right. Come on.
得了吧
For real.
沒開玩笑
Bring any sunglasses for me?
給我帶太陽鏡了嗎
Baby, I'm sorry. I forgot.
寶貝 對不起 我忘了
Here, take mine. Take mine.
給 戴我的吧 戴我的
Come on.
不會吧
They're good. They are.
確實是一副好眼鏡
They look great on you. Look at that.
看起來很適合你 瞧瞧
Where'd you meet him?
你和他在哪會面的？
It was in Carson, at the Hawaiian dude's house.
在卡森 夏威夷人的家裡
卡 森
Through your body.
身體發力
- What up? What up? What up? - Fucking nice.
- 好嗎  - 好
Yeah. Fool's in back.
在後面
You're mine!
再來！
- Donnie, what's good, man? - What's up?
- 唐尼 有什麼好東西 兄弟  - 好嗎
- Come on, man. Follow me. - Yeah, yeah.
- 來 跟我來  - 好 好
Hey.
嘿
Oh, shit. What's up?
嗯 好嗎
- Donnie, beer? - Yeah, yeah.
- 唐尼 要啤酒嗎？- 好
Thank you. Thank you.
謝謝 謝謝
So you spent some time at Wayside?
你在維賽德監獄待過？
Yeah, a little bit.
是的 待過一陣子
What do they serve for breakfast on Fridays?
每周五早上吃的是什麼早餐？
Silver dollar pancakes.
一塊錢的那種煎餅
Three of them.
3個
Where you from?
你是哪兒的人？
Hawthorne.
霍索恩
So you can drive, huh?
你說你會開這個？
Oh, I can drive.
哦！我太會開了
Drive.
開吧
You might want to put that seat belt on.
你也許該把安全帶系上
He liked how I drove, so, a week later, I did my first gig.
他喜歡我的車技 所以一周後我第一次參與他們行動
We hit this rave at a stadium.
我們把體育館給搶了
Got one.
找到一個
Minus the dye pack, is the count all good?
去掉有染料包的 其他的錢數對嗎？
The count is on.
對的
That's a lot of money right there, bro.
兄弟 這裡是很多的錢
Why don't we just call it a day?
我們收工吧
Really?
是嗎？
You want three in hot bills,
你是想只要這三摞贓款？
you looking over your shoulder for the rest of your life,
然後擔驚受怕地度過餘生？
or would you rather have 30 clean?
還是想要30摞乾淨利落的？
I'm just saying.
我就是說說
Let's just call it quits while we're ahead.
還是趁現在沒人查到我們 趕緊收手吧
Put it away.
放起來
We're trading up.
我們要用這些錢弄到更多的錢
All right. Fuck it. Let's do it.
好吧 去他的 我們幹吧
What happened to the cash?
錢去哪了？
I don't know.
我不知道
They don't tell me.
他們不告訴我
They don't talk much.
他們也不怎麼提這事
Yeah, people with things to hide never have much to say.
有東西要藏的人從不會多說話
So am I under arrest, or can I leave?
所以 我被捕了 還是我可以走了？
Nah, you just keep doing your thing.
還照舊生活
We'll be in touch.
我們會聯繫你
Yeah?
嗯
Horsepower, be at 1st and Central at 0800. Don't be late.
馬力 8點整到中心一號 別晚了
You always pick the same one.
你總是選這個的
Just go for it. I'm here.Do whatever you want.
隨便挑吧 有我呢 想買啥都行
Woo-hoo!
哇-喔!
Ran the prints on CAL-ID.
我把指紋在加利福尼亞偵察科鑒定過了
Got a hit on our dead guy from Angel City.
和一個天使城的人對上了
- Check your e-mail. - All right.
- 查下你的郵件 - 好
Name's Marcus Rhodes, from Oakland.
叫馬庫斯 羅茲奧克蘭人
ATF 全稱煙酒  火器與爆炸物管理局（Bureau of Alcohl Tabacoo Firearms and Explosives）
是一個隸屬於美國司法部（Dept of Justice - DOJ）  負責對煙酒槍炮徵稅  執法和釋法的機構
原隸屬於美國財政部  2003年1月24日移到司法部
ATF 通緝令
馬庫斯•羅茲
ATF was looking for him for gun charges.
酒精 煙草與火器管理局因持槍指控而要抓他
And more to the point that you were making before,
還有證明之前你說對了
he was stationed at Twentynine Palms the same time Merrimen was there.
他之前在二十九棕櫚村駐紮過 和梅利曼是同一時間
This is good. Give me the book on Merrimen.
那很好 給我梅利曼的檔案
Look to your right.
看你的右邊
You know what that is?
知道那是什麼嗎？
It's the bank for banks.
是專管銀行的銀行
Los Angeles branch of the Federal Reserve.
是聯邦銀行在洛杉磯的分行
It's the only bank that's never been robbed.
這是唯一一間沒有被打劫過的銀行
All the surrounding streets are wired for sound and image.
附近的所有街道都安裝了聲音和圖像檢測儀
Stand across the street and stare at the building for two minutes,
只要你站在馬路對面看著銀行超過2分鐘
you'll have security on your ass asking you politely to leave.
就會有保安禮貌的請你離開
If they see your face again,
如果他們在那看見你第二次
every Secret Service agent in the country is going to be looking for you.
全國所有的特勤部門人員都會來調查你
The place is case-proof.
這裡無縫可鑽
There have been 53 break-in attempts.
有53次試圖潛入的案例
Not one has got past the lobby.
沒有一次能越過大堂
That's why we're going to rob it.
很有挑戰性 而我們要搶的就是這家
Okay, here we go.
好 我們來看看
Laguna Niguel was in '06.
拉古拉 尼格奧 是06年進去的
Got caught for that, get sent up to USP Victorville SHU
他被捕後被送到維克托維爾舒監獄
until June of '16. Now give me the unsolved book.
直到16年6月 給我下未破案的文檔
As soon as you enter the lobby,
你一進入到大堂
computers run you through every law enforcement database in the country.
電腦就會自動在全國罪案聯網上核對你的資料
If you've got outstanding parking tickets,
如果你有未處理的停車罰單
they're going to know about it before you get through the first level of security.
在你未接觸到第一級的保安之前他們就都查清楚了
All the employees wear security swipe cards
所有員工都有門禁卡
that grant them access through the first set of man-traps.
這樣他們就可以出入第一道人工檢查關卡
Access is severely restricted.
出入是極其森嚴的
Two stories below street level is the vault floor.
地下二層就是保險庫樓層
By the way,
順便說一句
uh, his crimey...
這個嫌犯
- Levoux? - Levoux.
- 拉沃爾 - 拉沃爾
He serve with Merrimen?
-他和梅利曼一起服過役嗎？
Not only that, but they played football in high school at Long Beach Poly.
不止 他們在長灘工藝學校的時候一起踢過足球
- You've got to be shitting me. - No.
- 你他媽沒跟我開玩笑吧 - 沒有
Central Security, it's the nerve center for the Fed.
中央保安系統 就是聯邦的中樞神經
This is where the armored cars come in, drop off the money tubs.
這裡就是裝甲車出入裝卸錢箱的地方
Money tubs are handed off to the Fed employees.
錢箱會直接交給聯邦的員工
At any one time, there's anywhere between 500 and 800 billion dollars in there,
那裡一直都儲有5000到8000億美元
every millimeter of it covered by cameras, sensors, and motion detectors.
每一寸都被攝像頭和動作感應器所覆蓋
Yeah. What did they specialize in?
他們都擅長什麼？
I got this from the HR desk at Twentynine Palms.
這是我在二十九棕櫚村人力資源找到的資料
Close Quarter Battle Unit. Both saw combat in the Middle East.
近身突擊隊 兩人都在中東真槍實戰過
Levoux specializes in explosives, where Merrimen specializes in soldiering,
拉沃爾是爆破專家 梅利曼是實戰士兵
both MARSOC fast Marines.
兩人都是海軍陸戰特種兵快擊手
But there's a hitch.
但是裡面是有圈套的
The serial number of every bill is recorded in the Fed's database.
每一張鈔票的序號都是記錄在聯邦的資料庫裡的
So, if a note goes missing,
如果任何一張不見了 不管是為什麼不見
they're going to know exactly which one it is.
他們都能知道是哪一張
They're going to flag it. If that bill comes up again,
鈔票會被聯網標記 只要那張鈔票
whoever recirculates that cash, no matter where they are in the world,
在世界任何的一個角落再出現
that person can be tracked.
他們就能找到持有鈔票的人
Okay. Bosco, the peckerwood?
那啄木鳥博斯克呢？
He's a Huntington Beach kid, also MARSOC Marines.
亨廷頓海灘男孩 也是海軍陸戰特種兵
He did comms with them. He had a solid career.
他做過他們的聯絡員 前途光明
But he didn't serve together with the other guys.
但是他並沒有和其他幾人一起服役
He was the Wood Rep at Victorville when Merrimen was there.
梅利曼在維克托維爾的時候 他是他們的代言人
That's where they linked up.
他們就那樣混到一起的
Donnie was a Marine for a year and a half, then discharged.
唐尼做了一年半的士兵然後退伍了
So, the way I see it,
我覺得
that's the way all these niggas ended up working together.
這夥人就是這樣走到了一起
There's only two passports on the streets, sports and military.
我只看到這兩個關聯點 足球和服役
Every time the Fed receives a deposit from a bank,
每次聯邦從銀行接手存儲金
first thing they do is send that money up to the count rooms.
第一件事就是把錢都送去點鈔室
They run the notes through the counting machines.
錢被塞進點鈔機
They're accomplishing two things here.
兩個目的
First, they're double-checking the accuracy of the bank's deposit.
一 他們要再次檢查數目是否準確
If the bank is off at all,
如果多了少了
they're going to credit or debit the account accordingly.
就會在賬戶上做對應錢數的增減
Two, they're separating newer, fit currency from old unfit bills.
二 他們把新的鈔票和舊的損壞了的鈔票分開
But most importantly, they're erasing the serial numbers
最重要的就是 他們會把廢舊了的鈔票序號從系統裡刪除
of the old bills from the Fed system.
序號被刪除
Once those numbers are erased, to the Fed, to the rest of the world,
那些鈔票對政府和整個世界來說
that money has ceased to exist.
就已經不存在了
Wait, let's look at the unsolved cases.
我們來看看未偵破的案件
In '04, you have the Boller National Bank Hollywood job, okay?
04年的好萊塢博勒國家銀行搶劫案
They tunneled through the sewer system.
他們是在下水道挖了通道
Sophisticated, skill set, someone with access, unsolved.
很老練的 技術含量高 有人做內應 沒破案
Okay, in '05, you have the Fuerte armored car depot job.
05年 有弗爾特裝甲車被劫案
Blew the depot vault with shaped charges.
用聚能藥包炸開了保險庫
In the $100 count room alone,
光一百美元點鈔室
an average of $30 million is designated as unfit every day.
每天就有3億美元被變成廢紙
Between 4:00 p.m. and 5:00 p.m.,
每天下午4點到5點之間
all the cash gets shot out to the shredder.
所有費錢就會被運到粉碎機裡
It's all destroyed.
全都被銷毀了
$30 million turned to dust in seconds.
3億美元...幾秒內就灰飛煙滅了
It's then picked up by the Fed's waste management company
然後聯邦的合作垃圾公司
and brought out to the dump.
會把粉末運到垃圾場扔掉
If we can get to those unfit bills
如果我們能在這些廢鈔被送進粉碎機
before they go to the shredders and get out clean...
之前拿到它們 並全身而退...
You got $30 million nobody is looking for.
我們就能拿到可以安全使用的3億美元
Bingo.
答對了
In '06, you have Laguna Niguel.
06年 有拉古拉 尼格奧  跟之前一樣
Same thing, only this time Merrimen gets unlucky with the tail-light.
只是這次梅利曼不走運後車燈壞了
Goes to prison till 2016. Now in that time, while he was in prison,
服刑直到2016年 在他服刑期間
how many highly sophisticated, well-executed heists do we have?
我們遇見過多少個純熟 執行的極好的搶劫案呢？
None, but you're on a roll. Keep going.
沒有！但是你思路很對 繼續說！
The counter guy at the donut shop? Witness to the whole thing.
甜甜圈的收銀員 目擊了整個過程
They left him. Why?
他們為什麼要放過他？
Because they shoot uniforms, not unarmed civilians.
因為他們只打軍裝 不會傷害無武裝的平民
Exactly what they were trained to do.
那就是他們以前訓練出來的結果
Gangbangers, these are not.
普通黑社會小混混？他們可不是
Okay, these are our guys.
這些就是我們要找的人
We nail these guys, we solve all these cases.
我們把他們給搞定了 所有案子就都破了
This is the crew.
就是這個團夥
You still haven't told us how you can get past that security.
你還沒有告訴我們要怎麼通過安保
We're not going in this way.
我們不從這裡進去
We're going in that way.
我們從那兒進去
What's going on with Fräulein?
那小妞呢？
We can move on him anytime we want.
我們隨時可以逮他
蒙特利公園
- I pay minimum wage. - Okay.
- 我只給最低工資 - 好
Plus $3 for delivery. And you split the tip with me.
每單外賣佣金3美元 小費你我平分
You start Wednesday, 11:00.
周三11點開工
Thank you.
謝謝你
I don't really like the food there, but I'm down to go,
我不喜歡那的食物 但是我還可以去
- but you've got to pay this time. - I'm not paying it.
- 但是你得買單 - 我才不幫你買單呢
What?
啥
- I pay every fucking time. - What?
- 他媽每次都是我請 - 啥？
Get off your wallet, buddy.
別那麼吝嗇了
No, I forgot my wallet today, boys. I'm sorry.
我今天忘帶錢包了 孩子們 對不起了
- Again? - Yeah, again.
- 又忘帶？- 又？
Got an alligator arm.
你是鱷魚臂
I sat down at blackjack with $5, and I made $160.
我用5美元賭黑傑克 掙了160
Nicholas O'Brien?
尼古拉斯 奧 布萊恩？
Yeah?
幹嘛？
I suggest you take these.
我建議你收下這個
You're being served.
你被法院傳喚了
You kidding me?
你開玩笑嗎？
I'm afraid not.
沒有
What's going on?
什麼事？
You all right, bro?
兄弟 你還好嗎？
Yeah, I guess I'm getting divorced.
額 我想我可能要離婚了
He say "divorced"?
他說“離婚”？
Yo.
嗯
Welcome to the fucking club.
歡迎加入俱樂部
Now, go handle your business, big man.
去處理的你事情吧 大佬
Gas the jet.
上車
Fuck.
操
There's a closer view.
這是近距離細節
There was a rolling blackout in this quadrant four days ago.
4天前這裡有個停電盲點
Yeah, they've been happening a lot over the last few months.
對 上幾個月他們經歷了好多次
Okay.
嗯
They say they have full backup power, but actually they don't.
他們對外說他們有備用電 其實根本沒有
- They go into brown-out. - Yeah, prioritize the grid.
- 他們進入節電模式 - 優先供電
Priority, of course, is the vault. So everything in there stays intact.
肯定是優先給保險庫 所以保險庫很完好
But anything that is peripheral, like cameras in the hallway,
但是外圍的所有東西 比如走廊的攝像頭
shredders in the count rooms, everything else cuts out.
點鈔房裡的碎紙機都沒電了
To time it during another rolling blackout is going to be fucking impossible.
但是要預測下一次停電的時間簡直是天方夜譚
- So you want to simulate it? - Can we?
- 所以你想搞一次人為停電？- 我們行嗎？
Break in, have them go brown for about two minutes.
潛入 讓他們有兩分鐘進入節電模式
I'd say yes, but I'd like to have data to be sure.
我們假設可以 但我需要更多的數據才能確定
Great.
很好
Once we breach the count room, only thing left is the cameras.
我們一旦進入了點鈔室 只有攝像頭要擔心了
They run on their own power supply,
他們是自帶電源的
so they're unaffected by the brown-out.
他們不會被節電模式所影響
The solve here is we run an EMP burst.
解決辦法就是用電磁脈衝波
Should take out the cameras and motion for about 30 feet.
應該可以廢掉9米之內的監視器和動作感應器
Where you get all this information from?
這些信息是從哪裡得來的？
You don't have to worry about that.
你不需要知道
Just trust me when I say it's solid.
你只需要知道信息很可靠就行了
How we doing with the Telecal hook?
勾線做的怎麼樣了？
Couple days. Shouldn't be a problem.
還需要幾天 應該不是問題
How many handlers do you need?
你需要多少人支援？
Uh, gate B right now.
我現在在B大門
Strolling right into the Federal Reserve.
大搖大擺的走向聯邦儲蓄
Force leaving loading dock B.
武裝人員離開B卸貨口
聯邦儲備銀行   洛杉磯分行
中央安保
ID?
身份證？
Sign in, please.
簽字
Keep this on you at all times.
必須隨身攜帶這個 用第二區域的電梯
Second bay of elevators. Cafeteria's level 2.
到2層的用餐區
Buzz him in. He's good.
他沒問題 讓他進去吧
Smells good.
挺香啊
He's good. Let him in.
他沒事 讓他進去
- Sharon? - Mmm-hmm. That's me.
- 莎倫？- 是我
- How you all doing? - Good. How you are doing today?
- 你好 - 你今天好嗎？
- He's fine. - Thank you.
- 他挺帥的 - 謝謝
She ain't getting none.
她可釣不到你
Shut up. Really?
閉嘴！別這樣
Y'all have a good day. I'm gonna stay out of it.
- 祝你一天愉快 - 我可不插嘴了
- We will now. - You have a wonderful day.
- 肯定會愉快了 - 祝你一天愉快
Lunch. Dessert. Lunch. Dessert.
午餐 甜點 午餐 甜點...
Bye, sunshine.
再見 甜心
There he goes.
他出來了
Fed's got 82.
美聯儲那邊沒發現問題
Maybe it's part of his regular route.
也許這是他常規送餐路線之一
Delivering Chinese to the Fed,
給美聯儲送中餐
my left nut.
拉倒吧你
No. They're casing the joint from the inside.
才不是呢 他們在查看內部情況
Okay, go back.
我們回顧下所有案件
Other than cash,
除了現金
what else do they take from the casino in the stadium?
他們從體育館裡的賭場還偷走了什麼？
Fed deposit slips.
美聯儲存款單
- But those were probably in with the cash. - Or not.
- 但這些可能都是跟現金一起被偷的 - 也可能不是
Listen, what if they were taking the cash
聽我說 有沒有可能他們是用偷現金
to disguise the fact that they were really there for something else?
是為偷其他東西而打的掩護？
And then they take down an armored car that's empty. Come on, guys.
然後他們搶走了一輛空的裝甲車 想想啊 哥幾個
Look, remember what Donnie said.
回想下唐尼是怎麼說的
It's trading up. They're going big.
他們要弄更多的錢 他們將會有大行動
Hey, Nick, you can't take down the Fed, man.
嘿 尼克 美聯儲可不那麼容易搞定吧
I'm sorry, Merrimen's no dummy. It's impossible.
抱歉 梅利曼可不是傻子 這絕不可能
The Fed is the Olympics, and Merrimen is Carl fucking Lewis.
搶劫美聯儲就如奧運會奪金 而梅利曼就他媽是卡爾•劉易斯
I'm telling you,
我告訴你們
Fraulein's holding out on us.
小妞沒跟我們說實話
My gosh.
我的天
- Oh, he's here. - Okay.
- 他來了 - 好的
Damn, girl looking fine.
- 天哪 你看起來太美了 - 謝謝
Thank you. You look amazing.
你看起來很棒
How are you?
你好
- Looking good. - Thank you.
- 你看著真棒 - 謝謝
- This is my mom. This is Rolando. - Hi.
- 這是我媽媽 這是奧蘭多 - 嗨
- Nice to meet you. Rolando. - Hi, I'm Malia. Nice to meet you.
- 很高興見到你 我是奧蘭多  - 嗨 我是瑪莉亞 很高興見到你
- I see where you get your looks from. - Thank you.
- 我現在知道你這麼美是遺傳誰了 - 謝謝
Thank you.
謝謝
- Can I take that? - Oh, yeah, sure.
- 我來拿著這個 - 好
Um, Rolando, this is my dad.
奧蘭多 這是我爸爸
What's up, Mr. Levoux? Nice to meet you.
你好嗎 拉沃爾先生 很高興見到你
Let me holler at him for a second.
我想跟他單獨說兩句話
Let me talk to you, bruh.
來 我跟你談談
Honey, don't worry about it. Okay? They're just gonna talk.
寶貝 別擔心 他們只是說幾句話而已
So here's what's up.
這麼跟你說吧
For the past 16 years,
在過去的16年裡
my daughter's safety and protection has been my responsibility
保護女兒的安全是我的責任
and my responsibility only.
也是我唯一的責任
Now, for the first time in her life, I see I've got to hand you that responsibility.
而現在 在她一生中 這是第一次我要把這責任交給別人 也就是你
Don't fuck up,
別搞砸了
or your mama will weep as she has
不然你會讓你媽媽每天以淚洗面
to wheel your ass around every day the rest of your life.
推著坐輪椅的你潦度殘生
Now I worked on this, because I want to say this to you as nice as possible.
我練習過這段話 因為我想用最和氣的口吻告訴你
Do you understand?
你明白嗎？
Yeah. Yes, sir.
是的 先生
It's all right. It's all right.
沒事 沒事
Listen. Listen.
聽著
All he's trying to say is, it's wonderful to meet you,
他只是想說很高興見到你
and he wants you to have a beautiful evening.
他想祝你有一個美好的夜晚
I'll see you at 11:30.
今晚11點半見？
Yeah. Yeah.
知道了
- 11:30. Yeah. 11:30. - Good choice.
- 11點半 11點半 - 這就對了
I think he got the picture, bro.
我想他搞清楚情況了 兄弟
托倫斯
Beers and sake, let's go.
啤酒和清酒 走著！
- Have wine. - What the fuck?
- 喝酒 - 搞什麼的
Hey.
嘿
Buddy.
兄弟
Donnie, right?
唐尼 對嗎？
- Yeah. - Yeah.
怎麼了？
Yeah, spotted you at the gym the other day, yeah?
我那天在健身房見到你了
Yeah, man. How you doing?
嗯 你怎麼樣
What's up, fellows?
兄弟們 好嗎？
You play football at Long Beach Poly?
你之前在長灘工藝學校踢球？
You look familiar.
你看著眼熟
No, I'm not from around here.
不是 我不是這裡的人
What are you doing here? You work around here?
你來這幹什麼？上班嗎？
Enjoying my dinner, man.
我來這享受晚餐
- Really? - Yeah.
- 真的？- 是的
Food here sucks.
這的東西多難吃啊
Yeah. Yeah, we come here for the ass.
我們都是來這撩妹的
So I'll see ya at the gym, man.
那健身房見吧
Yeah. Definitely.
好的
Have a good night.
祝你今晚愉快
Number 55, right? That's how I remember you.
你是55號吧 我記得你的號碼
We wore the same number, 55, right?
你跟我一樣是55號 對吧？
I went to South Torrance.
我去過南托倫斯
Yeah, we played you guys a couple of times.
我們跟你們打過幾次比賽
You and all those fat-ass Samoans.
你隊裡有不少薩摩亞肥佬
Yeah, they were big, but, man, lazy motherfuckers.
這幫肥佬體格大 還很懶
Probably all that Spam.
我們把你們虐成狗
Yeah, we fucking crushed you guys.
我帶隊時就虐你們
Crushed you guys when I was there. Crushed you guys when you were there.
你帶隊也是挨虐
Still crushing you guys.
你們一直被我們虐
We've got family here, bro.
我哥們都在這呢
Don't really appreciate you popping off.
你要是能自己出去就最好不過了
All right. All right, man. No need to get all agro.
好吧 別激動 沒必要這樣
Was I being rude? Was I being rude?
我剛才說話傷人嗎？
- What? - Let's go order, bro.
- 什麼？- 走吧 該點菜了
Hey, look, man, listen.
兄弟 聽我說
You've got a beautiful family. Everything's all good. Excuse us.
你這幾個哥們真不錯 沒人想惹麻煩 我們這就走
Kampai.
走嘍
See you at the gym, Donnie.
健身房見了 唐尼
Have a good night, ladies.
女士們 祝你們今夜玩得開心
You a cop?
你是警察嗎？
No. Are you?
不是 你是嗎？
Get out of the car.
下車
Go!
那邊走
- Where's the wire? - Come on, man.
你把竊聽器藏哪了？
I'm not wearing a fucking wire, man.
我他媽身上沒有竊聽器
Man, I'm not wearing no fucking wire.
我說我他媽身上沒有竊聽器
Get up.
起來
How does he know you?
他怎麼認識你的？
Don't tell me it's from the fucking gym.
別跟我說你倆是他媽在體育館認識的
Look, I don't know him.
我跟他不熟
Smoke this punk.
崩了他吧
Talk, motherfucker.
說實話 你這混賬
I'm not no cop, all right?
我不是警察
Now he came to me. He know you.
是他過來跟我說話的 他認識你
He know all of you. But I ain't tell him shit.
他認得你們所有人 我什麼也沒跟他說過
He was sweating me. I ain't seen him since.
他嚇唬我 然後我就再也沒見過他
I thought he'd leave us alone.
我以為他不會來找我們了呢
So how much do they know?
他們知道多少？
Nothing.
他們什麼都不知道
I ain't tell them shit.
我什麼都沒說
I don't know nothing anyway.
我也什麼都不知道
And you know I'm the last person that would fuck this up.
你知道我是值得信任的
Now, if we've got to call it off, I get it.
如果任務取消 我能理解
But I know I ain't tell them shit.
但是我什麼也沒跟他說
Friday. Make sure he knows it's on.
告訴他我們周五行動
羅靈丘陵莊園
So good.
真不錯
It's true, though. It's true.
是真的 真的
Okay.
好的
How you doing, Nick?
最近還好嗎 尼克？
- I'm Nick. - Hello.
- 我是尼克 - 你好
- How are you? - Good.
- 你好啊 - 好
What's for...
嘿 晚飯..
- What's for dinner? - You smell like alcohol, Nick.
- 晚飯吃什麼？- 尼克 你真是一股酒味
Relax.
放鬆
I already ate.
我來之前已吃過了
Give me a pen, stud.
給我拿根筆 老兄
Nick, I was gonna call you.
尼克 我本想給你打電話的
I was gonna take you to dinner next week.
我原想請你吃飯
Just give me a fucking pen.
趕緊給我他媽拿根筆
Thanks, Rudd.
謝了 拉德
- I'm gonna hit the... - No, you're not.
- 我還是去... - 給我坐下
How's the wine?
酒好喝嗎？
Good?
好喝嗎？
That's pretty fucking good.
這酒挺他媽好喝啊
So I imagine I just, uh...
我想我就...
What, just sign anywhere, yeah?
隨便找個地方簽名就好了
Okay.
是嗎？
And I imagine it's assumed that if you were ever
如果你敢碰我的女兒
to touch one of my girls or, say, talk to them
敢跟他們說話
or, you know, even look at them,
哪怕只是看他們一眼...
I go boom-boom. You know what I'm saying?
我就會...你懂的吧？
But, I mean, that's self-evident, right?
我這說得夠明白了吧？
There's no need to put that in the contract, is there?
我想我剛才說的就不用寫進合約裡了吧?
- No, I didn't think so. - Nick...
- 尼克 - 我可不這麼想
Can you please go, Nick?
請你現在離開好嗎 尼克？
- That's enough, Nick. - Sure.
- 鬧夠了吧 尼克？- 當然
Come on.
起來
Come here. Give me a hug.
起來 跟我擁抱一下
Come on. We'll save a fortune in therapy.
這樣我們就不用費錢做心理咨詢了
Come on. Give me a hug.
跟我擁抱一下啊
There you go, huh, hoss?
這才對嘛
You've just always got to make a spectacle out of everything.
什麼事你都搞成種場面嗎？
There you go.
這才對嘛
Yeah, pretty much.
差不多吧
All right, Nick. I think it's time to go.
好了 尼克 我想你該走了
Come on, Nick, let's go.
好了 尼克 走吧
Call the fucking cops. That's what I'm saying.
報警啊你們
- Call the fucking cops. - I'm sorry, but it's time for you to go.
我很抱歉 但你真的得走了
Call the cops.
快報警
- I'm sorry... - Don't fucking touch me.
- 很抱歉 - 你別他媽碰我
- I'm sorry. - Do not fucking touch me.
- 抱歉 - 別碰我
- Come on, Nick. - Just, please go.
- 行了 尼克 - 請你快走吧
By the way...
忘了問你了...
- What do you want? - You hitting that from behind,
- 你想怎麼樣？ - 你是跟她玩的後入式的嗎？
and you're wondering what that thing is on her ass?
啪啪啪的時候還在想她屁股上紋的什麼？
- It's a tattoo of my name. - Nick, please...
- 告訴你 紋得是哥的名字  - 尼克 快走吧 求你了...
"Big Nick O'Brien."
"老大尼克•奧布萊恩"
Just a heads-up.
就是給你提個醒
Psst.
嘿
Call me.
別忘了打電話約哦
Take your time.
你們慢慢來
What happened to you?
你經歷了什麼？
Borracho, what do you think?
博拉科 你看我這身怎麼樣？
What the fuck was that?
你他媽之前說那堆話是什麼意思？
You spotted me at the gym?
你在健身房看到我了？
Tranquillo. All right?
別激動 好吧
Sit down.
坐下
I'll take it, Freddy.
這衣服我要了
Just give us a minute, okay?
我跟他單獨聊一會兒 好吧？
Look, they're not going to off you with this much heat, okay?
現在警察查得緊 他們不敢殺你的
When's this happening?
他們什麼時候行動？
Friday.
周五
Where?
在哪？
I don't know yet. All I can tell you is Friday.
我不知道 我只知道他們周五行動
TGIF, huh?
感謝上帝今天已是星期五了
You're protecting me on this.
你會保護我的 對嗎？
Fräulein,
小妞
we got your back, bro.
我們會保護好你的 兄弟
Don't worry about a thing.
不用擔心
Fuck.
操
Better wear your vest.
你們最好穿防彈衣
We're in.
準備行動吧
英格爾伍德
Z?
Pico Rivera Savings, Montebello Town Center.
皮科裡維拉銀行 在蒙特貝拉中心
Copy that, boss. See you at 0800.
收到 8點見
Tell the crew.
把信息告知全組成員
I did what you told me to.
我按你說的做了
星期五
You have fun?
玩得開心嗎？
He treat you right?
他對你還好吧？
Maloa.
瑪洛阿
You know I love you, right?
你知道我是愛你的 是吧？
I love you, too.
我也愛你
Come on, go to school.
去吧 上學去吧
There you go. Good job there.
乾得漂亮
McKenna!
麥坎娜
Hey, sweetie. Hey, sweetie.
嘿 寶貝
How are you? Good?
你最近怎麼樣 還好嗎？
What are you doing?
你在這幹嘛呢？
Well, you know, I was on my way to work
我正要去上班 路過此地
and thought I'd come by and say hello to my little monkey.
所以就想來看看我的小猴子
Is that okay?
行不？
How's everything at school? Okay?
在學校怎麼樣 還好？
- Yes, it's good. - Yeah?
- 是啊 還好 - 是嗎
And what about Auntie's house?
你阿姨家怎麼樣
Mommy and Cassady, are they good?
你媽媽和卡西還好吧？
What about the honey-bear? Honey-bear good?
你的玩具熊呢 還好嘛
Yeah? You miss me?
你想我了嗎？
All right, Pookie, better get back to class.
好啦 小寶貝 回去上課吧
When am I going to see you again?
我什麼時候還能見到你？
Soon, sweetheart. I'm gonna see you soon.
快了 寶貝 就快了
I want to come home.
我想回家
Me, too.
我也想
All right, you better get back to class, okay?
好了 你快回去上課吧
But I'm gonna see you later.
再見啦
Promise?
你保證會再來看我？
I promise.
我保證
Come on.
來 擊拳為證
Recess is over. Come on, kids. Come line up.
休息結束了 孩子們都回來吧
Go on, Pookie.
回去吧 寶貝
Bye, Daddy.
老爹 再見
Come on, McKenna.
快點 麥坎娜
Come on, honey.
快點 親愛的
Jock up.
帶好武器
Tac up, brother.
你好啊 老哥
No Fed?
不搶聯邦儲備局了？
Change of plans.
計劃有變
Pay attention.
聽好
Always keep your finger off the trigger until you're going to shoot somebody.
除非必須開槍打人 否則你的手指一定別放在扳機上
If and when that happens, safety selector switch.
如果必須開槍 先得打開保險
One for semi, two for full auto.
一下是半自動 兩下是全自動開火
Mag release.
準備好彈夾
Out with the old, in with the new.
沒子彈就換彈夾
Tug it. Make sure it's in there good.
檢查彈夾是否裝好
Slap the bolt home, you're ready for round two.
然後給槍上膛 準備下一輪射擊
Other than that, keep this thing pointed at the fucking floor.
不開槍的時候 槍口一定對準地面
- You understand? - Got it.
- 懂了嗎  - 明白
Go put your shit on.
穿戴好裝備
- Magazine, Borracho? - Yeah.
- 博拉科 給我來個彈夾 - 好的
- We good? - We good.
- 準備好了？ - 是的
皮科裡韋拉
儲蓄和貸款
蒙特貝羅
Suspects arriving on location.
嫌疑犯已到既定位置
We've got nothing for the DA. They haven't committed a crime yet.
我們沒有證據給地區檢察官看 他們還沒展開犯罪行動
They clear the bank, we take them down.
他們搶完銀行我們就動手抓人
- Stand by. - Roger that.
- 各單位就位 - 收到
Broad fucking daylight.
大白天的
They're packing big.
他們全副武裝
Ooh, shit. Look at these motherfuckers.
靠 看看這群混賬東西
Get down on the ground! Get down on the ground!
全都趴下 全都趴下
Down on the ground! Get down on the fucking ground!
趴下 全都趴下
Freeze!
都別動
Freeze! Don't move! Stay right there!
都別動 呆在那
Freeze!
都別動
- You two! Move! Get over there! - Get over here!
- 你們兩個 去那邊  - 去那邊
Hurry up!
速度快點
Get out here, now!
滾出來 速度快點
Move there now! Go! Go! Go!
快點
Move back! Stay right there! Now!
別動 待在那別動
Eyes to the floor!
臉對著地趴好
Listen up!
聽好
Everybody pay the fuck attention!
大家都聽好了
Eyes to the ground!
低頭趴好
'Cause I'm only going to say this once!
我只說一次
If you cooperate, if you follow directions,
如果你們合作 聽從指揮
you will not be hurt. We are here for money, not for you.
我們就絕不會傷害你們 我們只圖財 不想殺人
I want everybody lined up on the counter. Let's go!
所有人都出來沿著櫃檯趴好
Move down!
快點
Move down! Let's go!
Everybody behind the counter, come out front! Let's go!
速度快點 櫃檯後面的也都出來 快
Keep your eyes down and your mouths shut.
把頭低下 別亂看也別亂說話
On my command,
聽我命令
reach inside your pockets, remove your cell phones,
把兜裡的手機都給我拿出來
and put your hands in the air.
然後舉起手來
Everybody take two steps forward.
所有人 向前兩步
Now go down on your knees.
都跪下
All right! Cell phones right in here.
手機都扔進來
On me.
都老實點
Let's go. Put them in the box.
快點 手機都扔進盒子裡
Tie them up.
把他們手捆上
Go! Go! Go!
快快快
There will be no heroics today.
誰也別逞英雄
You guys go ahead and get comfortable.
老實地呆著
We're going to be here for a while.
你們得在這呆一陣子了
Anybody need to use the bathroom?
有想去上廁所的
Take a piss on yourself.
往褲襠裡尿吧
You. Get up.
你 起來
Stop.
別動
Sit down.
坐下
All right, I need you to calm down right now.
我需要你冷靜下來
Hey! Look at me.
嘿 跟你說話呢 看著我
Take a deep breath.
深呼吸
Good.
好
I know you already triggered the silent alarms.
我知道你已經按過無聲警報器了
So I need you to pick up the phone,
所以我需要你拿起電話
dial 911 dispatch, and explain the following.
撥打911後 按我說的跟警察說...
Go ahead and write this down.
你得把我的話寫下來
There's a 211 in progress, and we have hostages.
這裡發生211案件 劫匪有人質
Within one hour, they need to deliver $10 million
在一小時內 他們得給我送來一千萬美金
in unmarked small denomination bills to this bank
必須都是未標記的小面額鈔票
inside a department helicopter loaded with fuel.
要用警局直升機運來 加滿油
Tell them we plan on killing one hostage every hour until our demands are met.
跟他們說 不滿足我們的要求 每隔一小時 我們就殺死一名人質
No cops are to approach the bank.
不允許警察接近銀行
And if a negotiator even tries to contact us,
如果安排談判專家來 他敢張嘴
we will automatically kill another hostage.
我就馬上殺死一名人質
Is that clear? You got it all?
聽懂了嗎？你都記下來了嗎？
Go ahead and pick up the phone.
打電話吧
Any available units, we have a bank 211 in progress...
有外勤警隊暫時沒任務嗎？
Shit.
他媽的
...at the Pico Rivera Savings in Montebello
在皮科裡維拉銀行發生搶劫案 地址是蒙特貝拉
at 2891 Wilcox and Atlantic.
威爾考克斯路和亞特蘭大路岔路口 2891號
- Suspects are armed... - What the fuck?
- 嫌犯都有武器 - 該死 這幫混蛋
...and have taken hostages and are refusing a negotiator.
劫持人質 拒絕談判
What the fuck is going on? That's not their MO.
他們在幹什麼？這不是他們的以往手法啊
Call in, tell them we're on scene, have suspects under surveillance,
向總部匯報 我們就在案發地點監視
and to back the fuck off.
讓他們都撤退
This is LASD, we have surveillance on the bank. Stand down.
我們是洛杉磯縣治安官 我們正監視嫌犯
I repeat, have all units stand down.
請下令所有警隊小組撤退 我重複 全部撤退
It's bullshit. I can hear them already.
靠 我都聽到警笛聲了
What the fuck are they doing?
你們他媽的在幹什麼？
Stop!
停車
Get out!
出來
What the fuck are you guys doing, huh?
你們他媽的在幹什麼？
Asshole!
混蛋
What the fuck are you doing? What's going on?
你們他媽的在幹什麼？
You were running surveillance, and you let this shit go down?
你監視著嫌犯 還讓他們控制了銀行和人質？
It's our fucking case. We've been surveilling these guys for weeks.
這是我們的案子 我們監視他們好幾個星期了
That's what surveillance is!
監視他們
They commit a crime, and then we stop them.
就是想在他們犯罪的時候抓捕他們
Go. Go to the vault.
走 去金庫
Open it.
把金庫打開
Let's go. Come.
我們走 來
Sit. Sit down.
在這坐下
I'm going to put this on speaker phone.
我開免提
You're going to answer, but don't use any names.
你來接電話 但不能說名字
You understand?
懂嗎？
Hello?
你好
Hello, this is the Los Angeles Police Department.
你好 我們是洛杉磯警察
Who am I speaking with?
跟我通話的人是誰？
This is the branch manager.
我是這的分行經理
Sir, I need to speak with the person in charge.
我需要跟匪徒頭領說話
You are.
我聽著呢
Okay, good. Well, let me introduce myself. I'm Officer Parada...
好 我先自我介紹下 我叫...
I don't give a fuck who you are. Are our demands being met?
老子不在乎你是誰 我們要求的東西 你們都準備好了嗎？
Who am I talking with now?
現在跟我說話的是誰？
Answer the question.
回答問題
It's being worked on as we speak.
我們正在準備
But you need to understand...
但請你理解一下...
You just killed a hostage.
你害死了一名人質
God damn it!
該死的
- Get up. Get up! - No! No! No!
- 起來 - 不要啊
Come on, move!
起來
I didn't do anything. Please. What are you doing?
我什麼也沒做 求求你 你要幹什麼
- Come on. - No! No! No!
求求你 不要殺我
Fuck!
該死
- You were on it, huh? - Shit!
- 媽的 - 都在你們掌控下？
You're so full of shit, O'Brien...
你這蠢貨
You heard the demands, you stupid motherfucker!
你知道他們的條件
- Yeah. - You put a negotiator on? Christ!
還派談判專家聯繫他們？
- Fuck you! - Fuck me?
- 去你媽的 - 你罵我？
Yeah, fuck you!
罵的就是你
Fucking nice haircut, you fucking idiot.
你自己犯傻
Who are you fucking pushing now?
你他媽還推我？
Are you fucking kidding?
你他媽開玩笑呢？
- Get SWAT rolling right now! - You fucking pussy.
- 立即匯報總部 - 你這混蛋
Fucking Lobbin' Bob is angry!
你這傻逼還生氣了？
- All right, boss, let's go. Let's go. - Shitheads!
- 好了 老大 我們走 - 他媽的
- Let's go. - Fuck!
- 我們走吧 - 媽的
We've got a situation going on...
案子這邊有新情況發生
Shit!
媽的
What the fuck are you doing, Merrimen?
梅利曼 你在幹什麼呢？
Yeah?
說吧
This is the Police Department. Please don't hang up.
我們是警察 請別掛斷電話
My name's Danny,
我叫丹尼
I'll be your only contact. Nobody else is going to call you.
只有負責與你聯繫 除了我沒人會打電話給你
Is this the person in charge?
你是劫匪頭領嗎？
This is the branch manager.
我是分行經理
I'm speaking on the man in charge's behalf.
代表劫匪頭領跟你說話
Do you have a name, branch manager?
分行經理 你叫什麼？
Listen. They've already killed one of the hostages. A woman.
聽著 他們已經殺死了一名人質 是個女的
They will not speak to you again.
他們不會跟你聯絡
If you call back again before their demands are met, they'll kill another.
如果在他們的要求未滿足前 你再打電話來 他們還會殺死一名人質的
Just send what they want.
趕緊把他們要的東西給他們吧
The money and the chopper are en route,
錢和直升機在準備了
but it's going to take a little bit of time.
都需要時間來安排
You need to give me at least 90 minutes. Is this doable?
我需要至少90分鐘 可以麼
Okay. Don't call back.
可以 別再打電話了
What's the prefix here?
這個區域是哪裡
562. It's Long Beach.
長灘 562區
Hello?
你好
You watching?
你在看嗎？
Yup.
是的
So how the hell are you going to get out of this one?
你準備如何脫身呢？
Not sure yet.
我還沒想好呢
Did you get my number from her cell?
你從那個妓女那要到的我的電話號？
I ain't cuffing up.
休想讓我戴上手銬
That's okay.
無所謂
I didn't bring my cuffs anyway.
反正我今天沒帶手銬
Yeah, I can see that.
是啊 我看到了
Was that who I think it was?
是他嗎？
Yup.
是的
We've got a chopper that's gonna come down.
直升機到位時
The chopper is going to land right over here.
會在這裡降落
I've got two-door entry on one. One-door entry on two.
圖上顯示有一個雙門入口 兩個單門出
Breaching!
準備引爆
Well, they just blew the vault.
他們把金庫大門炸開了
What the fuck?
發生什麼了？
Federal Reserve, accounts receiving.
這裡是美聯儲 您是哪裡?
Hey, it's Al at Alameda.
我這裡是阿拉米達
We have a drop at Pico Rivera we need to schedule.
從皮科裡維拉銀行要運過來一批錢
How's Wednesday at 2:00?
您看安排周三下午兩點接受如何？
That works. You're confirmed for 2:00 p.m. the 18th.
可以的 安排在18號下午兩點 是嗎？
Great. Thanks.
是的 非常感謝
- We're here, yeah? - Yeah, that's us.
- 我們在這 對吧？- 是的
So what is this?
這是什麼？
This is the sewer line,
是污水管道
and according to this map right here, it's all cemented up.
如果圖紙沒錯的話 這都是水泥管道
Hey, where are we with the chopper?
直升機申請進行到哪一步了？
We're waiting on clearance.
還在等審批
Relax, they're not going anywhere.
別擔心 反正他們也跑不了
To hell with clearance. We've got to move.
還等個毛審批 我們必須行動了
O'Brien, hey!
奧布萊恩
Is he off his meds?
他是不是出門忘吃藥了？
Tell him to get the fuck back here!
跟他說讓他趕緊滾回來
Will you shut the fuck up?
能別嗶嗶了嗎？
Oh, fuck you.
去你媽的
We better go back him up.
我們得去支援他
Nick's heading to the front. We're on the move.
尼克奔正門去了 我們得去支援
Here we go.
行動
- Fuck! - Is he serious?
我了個去 他是認真的嗎？
Everybody okay?
大家都還好嗎？
Yes.
是的
Please, Lord, please, let me see my family again.
求求你 老天 救救我吧 我想再見到家人
- Nick! - Sheriff's Department.
- 尼克你在哪？- 洛杉磯縣治安官
Nick!
尼克？
Clear!
這裡安全
我這也安全
- The fuck? - Nick, what's your location?
- 他媽的 - 尼克 你在哪？
What's your location?
你在哪？
Hey, this is Al at Alameda again.
你好 還是阿拉米達給您致電 我不記得
I forgot to schedule a drop at the Pico Rivera Savings.
達皮科裡維拉銀行出庫的時間了
What do you have open today?
你們今天安排的是幾點來著？
Ghetto Bird, this is Silverback. We confirmed?
"黑貓" 我是"白貓" 時間確認了嗎？
Check. Appointment's at 2:45. That's in two minutes.
確認了 是兩點四十五 也就是兩分鐘之後
Pico Rivera.
運往皮科裡維拉銀行
Horsepower all set?
"馬力" 一切都準備就緒了嗎？
Yeah, I'm ready to go.
是的 都準備妥當了
They got you on a new route?
你們是新來的？
Yeah. Yeah, they just switched us over this week.
是啊 這周剛給我們調過來
All right. Let me get you guys' IDs, man.
好的 給我看看你們的證件
Yeah, sure. There you go.
好的 給你
All right.
好了
You're good to go.
你們可以過去了
- All right, thank you. - Open the gate. Have a good one.
- 謝謝 - 打開大門 過去吧
Oh, fuck.
該死
Pico Rivera Savings? 2.2?
皮科裡維拉銀行2.2？
Yup, that's us.
是的 是我們
Bring her up.
把錢車推上來吧
All right, ready. One, two, three.
準備 1 2 3拉
- Sign here. - You got it.
- 在這簽字 - 好的
You're new here, Mark?
馬克 你是新來的？
Yes, sir.
是的
You guys running a little bit late.
你們來的有點晚啊
Yeah, we ran into some traffic, so...
是的 我們來的時候有點堵
I don't know where they had you guys routed before,
我不知道你倆以前在哪運鈔
but we run a tight, tight ship around here,
但是在我們這 交接時間是非常嚴格的
so, if you're going to be late, have base call it in.
如果你們要遲到了的話 必須先打電話通知這裡一聲
Yeah, no problem. That's my fault. I just...
沒問題 這次是我工作有失
Just have them call.
記住下次打電話
On me.
跟我來吧
Hey, Luigi. Alameda's on deck. Check them in.
嘿 路易吉 阿拉米達那批錢運到了 你去接收吧
Copy that.
收到
New guys.
是新人
I'm going to step out for a minute.
我出去看看
How you guys doing today?
哥幾個你們好啊
- Good. All right. - Good.
- 你好 - 你好
How you doing?
嘿 你好嗎？
- All right, how are you? - Good, thank you.
- 還不錯 你呢 - 我也很好 謝謝
Sign that for me, please.
請在這裡簽字
All hundreds?
都是百元面值的嗎？
The first one's all hundreds. The second one is mixed.
第一車裡的都是百元面值的 第二車什麼面值的都有
We're a little backed up.
我們這邊有點忙不過來
All right, do what you can.
好的 盡快就行
Guys want to hang out, get a Coke or something? Appreciate you.
你們先等等 喝杯飲料什麼的吧 非常感謝
Thank you.
謝謝
We're going to need access to the recording off-site.
我們需要方圓250米地下管道檢查權限
Can you get that to us?
能搞定麼
- Understood. - You need professional help.
- 了解  - 你需要看心理專家
Desperately.
說得對
My bad last time. Your crime scene.
剛才是我不對 這現場交給你了
Silverback, this is Horsepower. I'm in.
"白貓" 我是"馬力" 我已就位
Greenpeace, this is Silverback. Horsepower is in.
"綠貓" 我是"白貓" "馬力"已就位
Roger that, Silverback. Lights out.
收到 "白貓" 現在關燈
Okay, here we go.
好吧 我們去看看
Johnny, we're fucking brown again, man.
強尼 又他媽斷電
Got to shut down. Pull them out of the count rooms.
停止一切工作 讓他們離開點鈔室
We're going brown.
停電了
We've got to shut down for a bit. All teams go ahead and take 10.
我們要關閉一會兒 所有人去休息吧
Luigi, come on.
路易吉 出來吧
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
好的
They went to brown. They're clearing out.
根據斷電應對程序 他們都撤出去了
- Let's lock it down. - Copy.
- 我們去把門都鎖好 - 好的
Get ready to go.
準備行動
Powering up EMP now.
啟動電磁脈衝
All clear here.
全部檢查完畢
Good to go.
可以行動了
You're clear. Go.
外面安全了 你出來吧
Shit. Check something out.
好像這出了點問題
What do you think it is?
你覺得是哪裡壞了？
Are the cameras up in the 100 room?
百元面值鈔票計數室的攝像頭壞了嗎？
Uh, negative.
壞了
555-01-43. 555-0143.
It's taking too long.
他們太慢啦
Tasty Orders.
這裡是訂餐熱線
This is Sharon at the Fed.
我是美聯儲的莎倫
Now, we ordered almost an hour and a half ago.
我一個半小時前定的餐
Now, I only have so much time on my lunch break.
我們午休都要過了怎麼還沒送來？
It coming! Be there in a few minute!
在路上了 馬上就送到
They just called for the Chinese.
他們剛打電話給中餐館
Hurry it up.
動作快點
Motion is out in there, too.
動作感應警報也失靈了嗎？
Yeah, man, we're still brown.
是啊 供電還沒恢復呢
You know, we better override. Power it up.
我們得重寫程序 趕緊啟動
All right.
是啊
Done.
搞定了
Okay. Better get that count, too.
讓他們重新數一遍錢
Shit, here comes security. Get down. Get down.
糟糕 警衛過來了 快藏好
Hey, man, we got to check this 100 count. Motion went off.
我們得檢查一下百元面值鈔票計數室 動作感應警報失靈了
Luigi...
路易吉你聽到了嗎？
Step on it. Step on it, quick.
快按住對講鍵 讓他們不能說話
Yeah?
怎麼了？
- Luigi. - Yeah?
- 路易吉 - 該死
Damn, dude! Luigi, you're stepping on the line, man!
路易吉 你占著線呢兄弟
Say again? Russell?
拉塞爾你說什麼
Hey, dumb-dumb. You've got to let go of the push to talk.
嘿 笨蛋 你得鬆開按鍵才能說話
What the hell is going on here today?
收到 我去找他
Luigi, man. He's stepping all over the line.
路易吉一直聯繫不上
He's hot-micing like a motherfucker.
這傢伙手忙腳亂的
He's in the cafeteria. Go ahead and get him.
他在食堂呢 去找他吧
All right. Roger that. I'm stepping out.
好的 收到 我過去看看
You're clear. Go.
你安全了 快動手
Holy shit.
老天爺啊
Luigi, you're hot-micing.
路易吉 你一直不鬆開對講鍵呢
You've got to let go of the talk button. You're stepping on the line.
你得鬆開按鍵才能說話
Dude, it's not me.
嘿 我沒一直按著對講鍵
Come on, we've got to check the 100 count. Let's go. Get Junior. Let's go.
我們得重新數一遍百元鈔票 叫上你的搭檔
Switch to line five.
轉到五號線了
You got about a minute and a half, two minutes. Let's go.
你還有不到2分鐘的時間了 速度快點
They're back. Get out.
他們回來了 趕緊撤退
Luigi, you see anything, man?
路易吉 你看到什麼了嗎？
Yeah, we're good. There's nothing back there but dust.
什麼也沒看到
What am I looking for?
你讓我來看什麼？
Don't worry about it, man. I'm gonna juice up the room. Run the count,
沒事 我要找點樂子 你再數一遍錢
- and make sure we're good, all right? - Copy that.
- 確保沒有任何問題 好嗎？- 收到
Where are you?
你在哪？
This is Horsepower. I'm in the vents.
我是"馬力" 我在排氣管道裡呢
Greenpeace, you're done. Cut out.
"綠貓" 你那邊任務結束了 撤吧
We are back up, brother.
電力恢復了
All teams, back to the count room.
全體注意 回到鈔票計數室
Get on with LAPD Central.
通知洛杉磯警局中心
Tell them we're running surveillance at 8th and Grand.
我們在第八和格蘭大道上 跟蹤監視嫌犯
Request a Code 5. We do not wanna spook the suspects.
代碼5 不要驚動嫌犯
Copy that. Putting in a Code 5.
收到 代碼5已生效
Am I tripping or was this full before?
是我記錯了嗎 我怎麼記得這裡原來是裝滿錢的？
Let's just check the count.
我們再數一遍吧
$712,200.
是712200美元嗎？
是的
Russell, the count is on.
拉塞爾 錢數沒錯
All right, roger that. Go ahead and clock out Alameda.
好的 收到 去查阿拉米達運來的錢吧
Take Alameda out.
去數阿拉米達運來的錢
The count was good.
錢數沒錯
But both of your bins were half-full.
但你兩個錢箱都是半滿的
Sorry?
你說什麼？
Your bins, they were half-full.
你兩個錢箱都是半滿的
That's how we got them.
給我的時候就是這樣
Next time, just put it in a cash sack.
下次來時 這點錢裝袋子裡就行
Makes things a lot easier.
不用這麼麻煩的
Try and work smart, not hard.
用腦子工作 別蠻幹
Okay, sounds good. Thanks for the advice.
好主意 謝謝
We would tip you, honey, but that just took too damn long, okay?
我們本來想給你小費的 但是你來得太晚了
I'm the only guy they've got delivering today. I'm sorry.
我們飯店只有我一個送餐的 抱歉了
Sorry, guys, let me see your drop confirmation again.
抱歉 哥們 我還得看一下你們的運鈔文件
- All right. - There you go.
- 好的 - 給你
Chinese food guy?
中餐餐館的？
Go on. Buzz him in.
讓他進去
Hold him there.
讓他在那等著
2:45
Yeah, send him through.
讓他過來
Come here for a sec, buddy.
過來一下 小夥
Yeah, man, I don't have you signed in.
我沒看到你進來時的簽名呢
Where's your name?
你叫什麼？
Come on, man, I signed my name with a dude from the last shift, man.
我簽字了啊 你上一班的人看著我簽的
I don't know what to tell you.
我不知道怎麼跟你說
Damn you finicky.
這飯菜可真"好吃"啊
- I'm getting my money back. - Okay.
- 我得讓他們退我錢 - 對
That's all I need.
確認完了
All right, you boys are good to go.
好了 你們可以走了
- Thank you very much, Officer. - Take it easy.
- 非常感謝 - 放鬆些
- You have a good day. - All right.
- 祝你今天愉快 - 好的
- Go on. Get out of here. - Thank you.
- 行吧 你走吧 - 再見
Yes, security in the lobby, please.
請幫我接大廳警衛
Lobby.
這裡是大廳警衛
Yeah, did you see a delivery guy?
你看到那個送餐的了嗎
Red shirt, light skin. About 6 foot.
他是個淺膚色黑人 穿著紅色上衣 差不多一米八高
- Wait, what? - Stop him.
- 怎麼了？- 別讓他走
You got eyes on the 1-2 side? We'll cover the 3-4 corner.
你們負責左側 我們負責右側
Copy that.
收到
Got held up at security. What's your location?
我剛在警衛崗耽擱了一下 你在哪？
South on Grand, just past Vernon.
在格蘭南大街 剛過弗農大道
Go right on Gage. Right on Gage.
右轉上了蓋奇大道 右轉上了蓋奇大道
Copy that.
收到
Move! Let's go! Get out!
下車 速度快點
- Come on, move! Move! Here we go! - It's cool.
- 下車 速度快點 - 別激動
- Come on, get down! Go! Go! Go! - It's cool. I'm cool, man.
- 快下來 - 別激動
Be cool, bro. Cool.
別激動
Fuck.
操
There he is. There he is. Red shirt. Two blocks ahead.
他在那 紅衣服的那個 往前開兩個路口
Eyes on suspect.
發現嫌犯
Walking eastbound on 9th, approaching Hill, south side of street.
他正向9點鐘方向奔希爾大街去了
Pull up in front of him, in front of him.
在前面截住他
Let's get this motherfucker.
抓住這個王八蛋
Let's ram his bitch-ass into the gate first.
先把他抓到車裡吧
Get in the fucking car! Come on. Get in.
他媽的上車 滾上車
Fuck.
他媽的
Hit him!
揍他
Motherfucker.
媽的 別亂動
太平洋地平線垃圾站
南大門
All right, let's go. Let's go. Let's get it done as quick as we can.
速度點 盡快完事好撤退
Little fuck.
你他媽的
Where is he? Where the fuck is he, asshole?
那個混蛋在哪？
Fuck.
混蛋
Fucking... Fucker!
把耳機給我拿下來 那混蛋在哪？
Give me the burner phone. Where the fuck is he?
把一次性電話交出來 他在哪
Pacific Horizon Salvage.
太平洋地平線垃圾站
In South Gate. That's the rally point.
南門 他們在那集合
Silverback, go.
我是"白貓" 說吧
Horsepower's burned.
"馬力"被抓了
Repeat that. I can't hear you.
再說一遍 我聽不清
Horsepower is burned.
"馬力"被抓了
He's done.
他廢了
I'm still clean. Where am I going, bro?
我現在還安全 我去哪跟你們匯合？
Fuck!
該死
Let's go. Let's go. You guys got it all?
速度快點 錢你們都收好了嗎？
- Yes, it's all in. - Pick it up.
- 是的 都在這了 - 好的 都帶走
It's good.
好的
Pacific Horizon Salvage. South Gate, Alameda Corridor.
太平洋地平線垃圾站 在阿拉米達支路附近
10-4. Headed to you.
我馬上到
What happened to the other two?
其他人怎麼樣？了
They got burned.
都被抓了
Eyes on suspects.
發現嫌犯
Black, four-door Suburban!
黑色四門雪佛蘭巨無霸
Heading southbound on Alameda.
我們正沿著哈囉大道向南開
Approaching Slauson Avenue. I need you to parallel me on Santa Fe.
馬上到勞森大道了 你們在聖達非跟我匯合
We got some traffic up ahead. What's going on?
前面堵車了 怎麼回事？
Corridor's backed up.
路堵死了
We just turned down Alameda Corridor, heading south.
我們剛從阿拉米達支路出來 正往南開
Shit.
該死
Coming up on suspect, six o'clock.
正在接近嫌犯 嫌犯在6點鐘方向
Shit.
真堵
Right lane is closed up ahead.
右翼隊伍正在接近
I repeat, right lane is closed up ahead.
我重複 右翼隊伍正在接近
You guys see that?
看到了嗎？
Twenty, 30 cars back. What is that?
20 30輛車後面的那車是警察嗎?
Is that...
是警察嗎？
Okay, we're at a stop, stop, stop.
好了 停車
Fuck backup. We've got to move now.
等不了支援部隊了 我們得行動了
Fuck.
該死
Yup.
是的
That's them.
是警察
- Give me my vest. - Yeah.
- 給我防彈衣  - 好的
Yeah, here we go.
好的 給你
Okay, we've got them pinched in. We've got to move before it opens up.
他們堵在那了 我們得在交通順暢之前抓住他們
Cuff him up.
給他戴上手銬
Be advised, suspects wearing body armor.
注意 嫌犯有防彈衣
No center mass shots. Limb and head shots only.
不要瞄準軀幹射擊 瞄準四肢和頭部射擊
Copy that. Go around right here.
收到 往那邊開
It's jammed up.
都卡住了
Good? Okay, let's go.
準備好了麼 出發
- Oh, shit. - What?
- 該死 - 怎麼了？
They're getting out of the car.
他們從車裡出來了
Z, go down the right.
Z 去右翼包抄
Gus, Borracho, center with me.
格斯 博拉科跟我走中路
Murph, stay on the left. Don't come in.
默夫 你在左翼 別往上衝
- Pass me the saw. - Fuck.
- 把自動步槍給我  - 操
Let's go.
我們上
Stay down. Stay down.
趴下
Get down. Get down.
- Sheriff's Department. Stay down. - Get down. Get down.
- 縣治安官 趴下 - 趴下
- Get down. - Sheriff's Department, stay down.
- 趴下  - 縣治安官 趴下
Get down. Get down. Stay by the engine block.
趴下 躲在發動機後面
Get down behind the wheel.
趴下 躲到方向盤後面去
Sheriff's Department. Lady, get in the car.
縣治安官 女士 回到車裡去
Oh, shit.
該死
Borracho!
博拉科
Moving!
換位置
Moving.
Gus, Murph, you two go across and cut them off, okay?
格斯和默夫 你們穿過去截住他們 可以吧？
Tony Z, you ready?
托尼•Z 準備好了嗎？
Let's go.
上
Moving!
換位置
Move!
換彈夾
Moving. Moving.
換位置
Mag change!
換彈夾
Moving.
換位置
Mag change.
換彈夾
Moving!
快走
Go! Go!
Tony, you okay?
托尼 你怎麼樣？
- Yeah, go! Go! - You okay?
- 上 上 - 你沒事吧
Fuck!
該死
Go!
快跑
Cover!
掩護他
Move.
快跑
Fuck!
該死
Brick wall! Brick wall!
他在磚墻那邊
Behind the brick building!
他跑到磚砌建築物後面去了
My kids...
我的孩子
You're in His hands now.
你跑不掉了
You hear me?
聽懂了嗎？
Fuck!
該死
Don't do it.
別逼我
Told you.
早跟你說過了吧
Yeah. You did.
是啊 你說過
What the fuck?
什麼鬼
You see this?
你看這個
Here. Do those.
幫我都打開
Oh, shit.
該死
So what? They were going to make fucking snow globes?
他們弄這東西做什麼 雪景球嗎？
Like 10,000 of them?
做一萬個？
You check on the boys?
去看隊員們怎麼樣了沒？
Yeah, I'm going to roll to the hospital.
我會去醫院看一眼他們
You gonna call Borracho's wife?
你要給博拉科的妻子打個電話嗎？
Yeah.
打啊
All right.
好的
This won't go to Harbor.
他們本計劃去海港的
I'm sorry you lost one of your guys.
你失去了一個夥伴 我深表遺憾
Thanks.
謝謝
You all right?
你還好嗎？
Yeah, I'm okay.
我還好
Yeah.
我沒事
Nick, you've got to stop smoking, man.
尼克 你得戒煙了
Here.
試試這個
It's organic.
有機的哦
You know everything was accounted for at the Fed, right?
這些都會歸功給聯邦調查局 你知道的吧？
Apparently so.
當然知道
Hey, is Donnie around?
唐尼在嗎？
He quit.
他辭職了
So you haven't seen him anywhere?
你在附近有再見到他嗎？
I said he quit.
我說了 他辭職了
Two days ago.
兩天前辭的
You want a beer?
要來瓶啤酒嗎？
Very much so. Like 50.
一瓶哪夠 我想喝50瓶
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
- 謝謝  - 不客氣
言多必失
禍從口出
Did you see that new chick? Little fat-ass?
你看到單位新來的小妞了麼？
The new girl who works down the hall?
就是臀部很性感的那個？
What's going on, gentlemen?
哥幾個最近怎麼樣？
- Gentlemen, good to see you. - Yo!
哥們 你還 真高興你能來
- Good to see you. - Your wife know where you are?
- 你好嗎？- 你妻子知道你來這裡嗎？
How did you get that job?
你是怎麼拿到這份工作的
Can you actually count?
你真的會數數麼
I'm in complete control of my environment.
我能控制整個環境
People don't even know.
沒人能知道我怎麼做到的
聯邦儲備銀行洛杉磯分行
Fucking Fräulein.
他媽的小妞
倫 敦
What's going on, boys?
各位兄弟
How you doing? You good?
還好嗎？都還不錯嘛？
Some beers?
要喝點啤酒嗎？
Hey, guv.
嘿 服務員
A round of beers for my mates.
給我這些哥們上酒
And for you?
你想喝什麼？
I'm easy.
我要求不高
I don't know.
想不到喝什麼
Surprise me.
你幫我選個好的吧
I can do that.
好的
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- 乾杯 - 乾杯
So why you come to me?
你為什麼找我？
You're a beast, man.
你很凶悍
Plus, you're the only one that can pull this off.
而且除了你也沒人能幹成這事
Listen.
聽著
We do this, I call the shots.
如果我答應幹這票的話 就得我說了算
My crew, my job, not yours.
得用我的人 這票算是我的 不是你的
Got it?
懂了麼？
- Completely understand. - That's the way it has to be.
- 我懂 - 就得這麼來
That's it.
就這些
It's my baby.
這都是我的寶貝
That's what I've got.
我就弄到這些
How did you get a hold of all this stuff?
你怎麼弄到這些的？
You got this all at that bar?
你在酒吧就能弄到這些東西？
Collected it over time.
我費了很多時間才收集到這些的
Wow.
哇哦
Job for Superman.
這是超人才能幹的活
Cheers.
乾杯
Thank you. I love when you call me Princess.
謝謝 我很喜歡別人叫我公主
You work across the street?
你在街對面上班嗎？
Yeah.
是啊
Diamond exchange?
在鑽石交易所？
That's right.
是啊
Beer's on me.
這酒算我請你的